Blustering
Behavior
Word Bluff
Blustering Behavior
JesusP (Wonderful Opportunity!)
Kagamine Len
Kagamine Rin
Song
Composition
Illust
Translation/Encode
Video
Rakuchii
TsunaguSubs
(with permission from JesusP)
MiRA
Sora
Attribute
Genius
Every day is boring from the start
I'm surrounded by other kids as far as I can see
Allow me to clarify my circumstances
I'm always more grown-up and dangerous than my appearance suggests
The girl who's saying that seems to be
an all bark but no bite chuunibyou for the most part
so it's better if I don't get involved
By the way, why is she looking my way, huh?
Aw, crap...time to run!
B-B-B-B-Big Brother
Tsukasa
Attribute
Huh?
Are you serious?
I'm totally serious
I should be smarter than everyone else,
*See description
but you won't understand...
Don't give me that BS!
Welcome, words of truth!
Meet the Tatemae with a barrage of kicks!
There's no way I can lose to anyone,
so I can do it myself!
When the brat was thinking that
she stubbornly got all overconfident "by herself"
(Th, th,...that's not true!)
Clashing as you become covered in mud,
search out your ideal self!
Intermission
Let's get back
to the topic
My life is ridiculous
Dislike
Trouble
Hate
Human beings are always happy to spout nonsense
Truly amusing, isn't it?
disgusting things settle in my stomach as I laugh
I don't get what you're thinking,
kicking it everywhere that second with your severe lack of sleep?
Meanwhile, I'll finish off
this Tatemae -monster- by myself just as I envisioned!
- Boring, doesn't understand -
...I'm not blustering
- Good-for-nothing, disgraceful -
I'm not like that!
Fear
Defeat
Loss
Insanity
Isolation
Separation
Sadness
I'm still searching for my own unique reason to live -identity-
L-L-L-L-Leave it to me!
Wh, who is that?
Your Honne has matured
Keep this in mind so you can grow up, 'kay?
Let me see your inner potential!
Show me words of truth!
Crush the lies -fakes- of this world!
Expose the pure, real
Run?
feelings!
Victory
Confidence
Will you appreciate what you can't describe now?
Look, I'm a beautiful girl on the outside...
(Wh-wh-wh-wh-what are you saying...)
and a user of mighty powers becoming as wonderful on the inside
Sorry for being too much of a genius
Oi
Blustering Behavior
Word Bluff