Let this voice
and song of mine
carry midnight starlight
toward the lonely you
as I go to meet you
before the sun rises
I wonder if I can see you again
and reach you
Even if you were to go blind,
this light would still be
remembering you
Unending Dream
I found your name
deep in my heart
I ended up knowing
you were scared of waking up
When the morning comes,
you will
collect and assemble
the broken pieces
alone
yet again
and it will be goodbye
again just like always
Let this voice
and song of mine
carry midnight starlight
toward you of tomorrow
as I go to meet you
before the sun rises
I wonder if I can see you again
and reach you
Even if your tears were to fall,
this light would still be
remembering you
I found a door that wouldn't open
deep inside my heart
I ended up knowing
you were scared of being loved
You who locked the door,
all alone
yet again,
whispered,
"Please don't change."
to everything
It's goodbye again
just like always
Let this voice
and song of mine
carry midnight starlight
toward you of yesterday
as I go to meet you
before the sun rises
I wonder if I can see you again
and reach you
Even if I myself were to go blind
this light would still be
remembering you
You realized
your
last scene
was near
as the moonlight
shone on you
Again, just like always-
Now, this voice
and this song of mine
rains down midnight starlight
for your sake
When the sun rises,
it will be by your side
Since I just saw you
and reached you,
even if you were to reject it
this light would still be
remembering you
Translation/Encode: TsunaguSubs
Thanks for watching!